{
    "subject": "resource/Fern_Emmett",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Oakland,_California",
    "human_readable": "Fern Emmett was born in Oakland, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.968513011932373,
            "question": "Was Oakland, California a significant place for Fern Emmett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9169104099273682,
            "question": "Are there any notable events connected to Fern Emmett's birth in Oakland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9091963171958923,
            "question": "Where was Fern Emmett born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9001468420028687,
            "question": "In which state was Fern Emmett born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8219197392463684,
            "question": "Is there any connection between Fern Emmett and Oakland beyond her birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7176004648208618,
            "question": "What city is associated with Fern Emmett's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45566248893737793,
            "question": "Where did Fern Emmett likely spend her childhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3712351620197296,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Fern Emmett's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3689054846763611,
            "question": "What is known about Fern Emmett's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3619682192802429,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Fern Emmett?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fern Emmett was born in Oakland, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8102_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Fern Emmett's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8102_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Fern Emmett's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8102_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Fern Emmett likely spend her childhood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8102_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8102_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8102_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8102_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8102_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8102_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8102_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8102_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8102_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8102_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8102_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Fern Emmett was born on March 22, 1896, and she was born in Oakland, California, USA."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information in the documents supports that Fern Emmett was born in Oakland, California. Multiple documents provide this detail, thus confirming the statement as correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}